I'm in an unknown city
with a real in your pocket
and ninety days to set up a business
I live inside the Chevette and today is the day
nineteen
ha ha ha
I take a shower at the gym or gas tax
clean showcase
clean chair
dog ride
I hand over pamphlet and sell truffle
for now
here I keep my clothes
I made these cardboard plates
with garbage bag so the light does not enter
to be able to sleep well
but it always ends up leaking
bank is broken
there's water I fill at the gas station
sound box so I can hear my music
and now I've taken the passenger seat over there
and i can invest in a certain bed
of course I'm wrong bro
if I keep investing in
comfort for EU to sleep here in 1 Chevette
I'll never leave it Dude
if EU accommodates me
I do not prosper
I will not fetch
new things for my life that I deserve
instead of EU investing in a bed
now i'm investing in my business
and I will show you
what are
here are my other sources of income
I separated this space here ó
to save only the Cocoa Show truffles
and the side here
there is 1 other enterprise that I do that I invest
I'm trading this here for this
but why did i take out the bank
so i'll show you what my plan is
arrive there
this whole space here that
I took out the bank
I will put a cage to transport
dog and i can do a service now from dog Uber
I can take your dog on the train
your dog for a walk or in the pet shop
and of course
I will have an additional 1 so
in life is as follows
or you increase your capabilities
or you lessen your dream
the choice is yours
everything is on
slowly
company Rica
poor game
but if you invest in a bed
on Chevette you will have better sleep quality
who said i want to stay
sleeping in a makeshift bed inside a Chevette
bro i know the perrengue i pass
my brother
if i want better conditions
i need to improve my skills
simple as that old
until tomorrow
this chicken is going to be really crazy